大家好，我是月見大人。
雖然很多人可能不認識我，但我一直在福岡從事服飾店工作直到一月。
幸運的是我能在店裡舉辦畢業活動，所以拍了這支影片紀錄我工作的最後一天。
我的桌面頻道
不好意思。
早安。
這是我今天的穿搭。
我拿到了自己的畢業紀念限定T恤，所以就穿上這套搭配。
是不是很可愛？
我還把頭髮弄成符合這套風格的造型。
今天我會拜託朋友幫我拍攝。
我要去剪頭髮了。
這真的好可愛。
It's so cute.
It's like purple.
It's shiny.
I put a lot of my favorite characters on my
eyebrow.
This is why my shoulders are always bent.
Cute.
It's shaking a lot.
It's the same as the illustration.
Yes, I was conscious.
I was going to make it two, but I was running too much.
You ran too much.
Cute.
Many customers came to my store right away.
I'm grateful.
My job is mainly to take photos and post them on social media.
I think the fun part of being a customer is that I can choose the special clothes of each customer.
I feel happy to hear good news such as the participation clothes of my favorite idol, the clothes I wear on dates, and the clothes I got praised for the day after tomorrow.
I was talking seriously, but it was a very meaningful job.
I'm going to buy the clothes and go to the store.
Cute.
I'm so happy to hear good news.
Thank you.
I remember that I have to close my eyes.
I'll give you a tear bag.
I'm going to close my eyes.
Cute.
I think the top part is cute.
I took photos of the time during the graduation event and gave them autographs and dates.
I like this smell.
I'm writing my name on this day.
I'm sorry.
I don't think it's dry. I'll give you this.
Thank you.
Super?
I don't have much.
It's just a little.
I took two photos with my smartphone and talked with the customers who came to see me.
I'm going to buy clothes.
I was happy to see many customers who were friendly.
I was happy to talk with many customers who were friendly.
But I was too conscious of them and made a mistake.
I wrote "Wan" on the cat.
I was stupid to write "Wan" on the cat.
I'm going to buy clothes.
I was too conscious of them and made a mistake.
I was happy to see many customers who were friendly.
I'm going to buy clothes.